<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://lightningspirit.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://lightningspirit.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-09-25T02:24:37+01:00</updated><id>https://lightningspirit.github.io/</id><title type="html">Lightningspirit’s Blog</title><subtitle>Programmer, Hacker, Architect, Entrepreneur, Story Teller, Musician. Mathematics and Astrophysics passionate. User Experience lover. I'm just a spiritual being having a human experience.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="https://lightningspirit.github.io/2017/09/24/hello-world/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!" /><published>2017-09-24T23:30:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-09-24T23:30:00+01:00</updated><id>https://lightningspirit.github.io/2017/09/24/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lightningspirit.github.io/2017/09/24/hello-world/">&lt;p&gt;Often, the first post of a new blog has to explain the purpose, the reason why one starts to write something entirely new. Sometimes, the reason just urges and grows from the bottom of your deepest desires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some years ago I owned a personal website on lightningspirit.net domain, filled up with some crazy and “unimportant” stuff even with thoughts that nowadays would make me blush… whatever!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to write things about my daily activities, coding, web development, music, etc, and, when I remember those days, I recall how enjoyable it was to write something and get it published right away at the same day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, owning a blog is like having your very own virtual space, a unique piece of your fine art and your thoughts. There’s no “buzzing”, no “home feed”, no “profile page”, nothing that would make it spoil your words with fragments of existentialism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe, this is the best reason I can provide for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer me and my lovely one, we spent over 2 weeks in some Azores Islands, in the middle of Atlantic Ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Terrific&lt;/em&gt; is the word I use to describe this experience. A naturally harvested paradise, an archipelago of 8 islands mixing naturally crafted landscapes where one can hike towards small villages 30 minutes away from central towns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/azores-green-mountain-ocean.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;Sao Jorge Island, Azores, while walking to Faja de Santo Cristo.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Sao Jorge Island, Azores, while walking to Faja de Santo Cristo.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Azores was &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_the_Azores&quot;&gt;allegedly first dicovered by Diogo de Silves&lt;/a&gt; in 1415. He was the one who found the most eastern cluster (&lt;em&gt;Santa Maria&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Sao Miguel&lt;/em&gt; islands). As the time pass, some other discoveries took place during that century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most convincing island is &lt;em&gt;Sao Jorge&lt;/em&gt;. Its natural beauty with all thi fantastic landscapes and almost all seasons happening during the same day, makes it one of my favorite, I must say!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yy4-lEeNX-o&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Faial&lt;/em&gt; Island is where most of the trans-atlantic ships take a rest and drink some &lt;em&gt;Gin do Mare&lt;/em&gt;  at &lt;em&gt;Peter’s Café Sport&lt;/em&gt;. It’s very well known at the space this is the spot where sailors stop by for a couple of days enjoying their meals. It’s been around there serving transients since the second half of 18th Century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/azores-faial-peter-cafe-sport.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; alt=&quot;Peter's Cafe Sport, Horta, Faial, Azores.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Peter’s Cafe Sport in the ciry of Horta, Faial island, Azores.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like all other islands, Faial also holds a very volatile weather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe class=&quot;embed-responsive-item&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WBhPF8_qaYc&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in visit Azores, go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.visitazores.com/en&quot;&gt;Visit Azores&lt;/a&gt;. There’s lot of information you can use to help in your trip.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lightningspirit</name></author><summary type="html">Often, the first post of a new blog has to explain the purpose, the reason why one starts to write something entirely new. Sometimes, the reason just urges and grows from the bottom of your deepest desires.</summary></entry></feed>